Friends, are you welcome back to the channel?
So today we will discuss
how much salary does Link provide to Link Advisors or Link Agents
and whether Link Agents
get salary or not or is it just a
rumour that they get salary or only
commission is provided. If you
want to know the answer to all these questions then stay tuned to
this video.
Friends, if we talk about normal Link
Advisors, who are normal Link Advisors, Link does not provide
any kind of salary or
stipend to them, Link only
provides them Link commission on the policies brought by them, but if we
talk about special concepts of Link,
whose names are Richa and CC, then you
get
Career Agent in that, whereas the full form of CCA is
City Career.
Apart from Link Commission, the First Air
Agent gets Rs. 4000 per month for the first 12 months and
after that, for the next 12 months, he is
provided a salary at the rate of Rs.  It is of the category which
we call stipend and not salary,
so for the first year it became
₹60000 at the rate of 5000 per month and for the second 12
months i.e. for the second year it became ₹
48000 at the rate of 4000, so the total amount which is given
extra to the Link Richa agent apart from the commission
is ₹18000 and
if we talk about CCA agent then they are
given salary in the first 12 months itself which
is fixed at ₹7000 i.e.
they are provided extra Rs.84 thousand
apart from the commission, so friends I hope
you liked this information, do like and
subscribe